websiteurl.co.uk 2002-06-03

# Capitek plc - Search Engine Positioning and Submission Specialists

The following information describes how we handle the information we gather about visitors to our customers' Websites as well as information about our customers' visits to our Websites. 

**General Information**  
**Capitek plc** ™ is firmly committed to the privacy of customers and visitors to its Websites. We are equally committed to the privacy of the data we collect for sites using our Products and Services, and the visitors who frequent those sites to which they apply. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for www.capitek.com. Other **Capitek plc** ™ Websites may have different policies.

**Capitek plc** ™ does not use client data to send marketing material other than regarding pertinent products and services for that client. Clients and users of the **Capitek plc** ™ Website will only receive responses to specific and general enquiries, customer or client queries and requests for information or quotations, courtesy communications, confirmations of instructions and/or orders.

If you do not wish to receive any mailings from **Capitek plc** ™ please send an email to [unsubscribe@capitek.com ](mailto:unsubscribe@capitek.com) putting your name as the email title.

**Privacy Statement for Visitors to Websites**

**Privacy Principles**

Because your privacy is important to us, **Capitek plc** ™ conducts its Business under the following principles: 

**Principle 1 - No Collection of Personal Information**  
**Capitek plc** ™ does not collect personal information such as name, age, telephone number, eMail and mailing address from visitors to our Customer's Websites. 

**Principle 2 - No Combination of Browsing and Web Traffic Information with Personal Information**  
Since **Capitek plc** ™ does not collect any personal information, we do not combine traffic analysis information with personal information such as name, age, phone number and mailing address. 

**Principle 3 - No Aggregation of Individual Visitor Traffic Patterns across Multiple Sites**  
**Capitek plc** ™ does not collect individual profile information for visitors across multiple Websites and does not aggregate information from any other sources about browsing patterns of individual visitors across multiple Websites. 

**Principle 4 - Use of Anonymous IP Address**  
IP addresses are recorded by every Website on the Internet. **Capitek plc** ™ collects such information as well, but does so exclusively for the following uses: (1) anonymous statistical purposes; or (2) administration of our Website and Servers, and to improve our Services in general. 

**Principle 5 - Anonymous Use of Cookies**  
It is **Capitek plc'** s™ policy to use Cookies only for more accurate anonymous Traffic Analysis. The Cookie information does NOT include personal data such as name, age, phone number, eMail address or mailing address. In addition, **Capitek plc ™** does NOT link Cookies to personal data such as name, age, telephone number, eMail address and mailing address. Most browsers are initially set up to accept Cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your Browser to reject Cookies. 

**Principle 6 - No Individual Profiling**  
**Capitek plc** ™ does not create individual Profiles for visitors. **Capitek plc** ™ does not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor. **Capitek plc** ™ collects data in aggregate form and data is not recorded or stored for individual visitors. 

**Principle 7 - Limited Use of Cookies**  
**Capitek plc** ™ uses Cookies to track items such as the time/date of the visit, the time/date of last visit, the page viewed, the referrer, transaction information for eCommerce pages, and other data. The Cookies never include personal information such as name, eMail or mailing address and telephone number. We do not collect such information and visitors that we track can not provide us with personal information through normal movement across a Website. As we do not build a database of individual visitors, the data that we do collect is never stored in any individual user Profile; the data collected serves only to update aggregate counts allowing our customers to monitor traffic on their site. Visitors can also reject Cookies on their Browser. 

**Principle 1 - Your Information is Confidential**  
All the statistical information we compile from your Website is considered confidential. Statistics about your Websites are protected by Restricted Access Protocols. To ensure this privacy, our Data Center is protected by industry standard security technology, such as firewalls and security analyzers using SSL encryption to protect transmission of data. 

**Principle 2 - WebTrends Has Limited Access to your Information**  
**Capitek plc** ™ will not access, modify, or otherwise divulge the statistical information we compile from visits to your Website, except for the express purpose of generating reports which have been authorized by you or otherwise agreed to by you, or unless acting under a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of **Capitek plc** ™; (3) enforce the **Capitek plc** ™ Terms and Conditions; or (4) 'Troubleshoot' any Service problems. 

**Principle 3 - No Site-Specific Data is Ever Divulged**  
**Capitek plc** ™ compiles statistics across all the Websites utilising it's Products and/or Services and concerning certain broad categories, such as Internet Browser usage and screen resolution. This information is presented only in an aggregate form, and in no event will we present specific site data without permission. 

**Principle 4 - Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make a Website more useful by personalising information for visitors and by storing information about your preferences on a particular site. The use of Cookies is an industry standard, and many major Websites use them accordingly to provide useful features for their Clients and Customers. 

**Principle 5 - Personal Information**  
**Capitek plc's** ™ secure online purchase registration form may require users who signed up for our service to give us contact information (such as their name, date of birth and contact details including an eMail address), and financial information (such as their Credit Card number). Personal and financial information that is collected is used to check the user's legitimacy, bona fides and qualifications for registration and to bill the user for **Capitek plc** ™ Products and Services. **Capitek plc** ™ does not store such information linked to a cookie. We may use this information to contact users accordingly with the provision of **Capitek plc** 's Products and Services and for **Capitek plc's™** internal Marketing purposes only. 

**Privacy Disclosure and Indemnification**

You hereby agree to defend, at your expense, any action brought against **Capitek plc** ™, arising out of your use of the Products or Services with any third parties or from your willful misconduct. You will indemnify **Capitek plc** ™ from any costs, damages and fees incurred by **Capitek plc** ™, which are attributable to such a claim or action. 

Please don't hesitate to contact us if you have any queries or would like further information about **Capitek's** ™ Privacy Policy email [privacy@capitek.com](mailto:privacy@capitek.com)
